<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sandipb.net : references</title>
    <link>https://ref.sandipb.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on sandipb.net : references</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 19:15:21 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ref.sandipb.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Git</title>
      <link>https://ref.sandipb.net/git/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 19:15:21 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ref.sandipb.net/git/</guid>
      <description> References  Using Git submodules: No matter how less I want to use Git modules, I seem to need them all the time. Most of the time, whenever I use a program like Hugo which has external extensions, I end up needing submodules.  Common procedures  Remove a Submodule within git: Adding a submodule is easy, removing is such a pain  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golang</title>
      <link>https://ref.sandipb.net/golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 18:06:18 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ref.sandipb.net/golang/</guid>
      <description>Best practices  Gophers, please tag your releases (Dave Cheney) - Tag your releases in preparation for better dependency tools coming in the future (2016-06-24) Idiomatic Go tricks - By Mat Ryer, companion blog post (Youtube, 2016-09-09)  Important third party libraries  GORM: A popular Go ORM. Very well written usage documentation. CLI (Command line libraries):  urfave CLI: Formerly codegangsta/cli. Man page like extensive help formatting. Cobra: Integrates with Viper, a config management library   Implementation articles  Error handling in Upspin: An interesting article by the legendary Rob Pike about how to use custom error types to provide more meaningful messages in an app with many components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome</title>
      <link>https://ref.sandipb.net/post/collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 17:33:24 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ref.sandipb.net/post/collection/</guid>
      <description>This is just a collection of my references on various topics.
Current docs include:
 Golang Git  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>